Finding Aid for Chester A. Graham Papers 1921-1980
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Chester A. Graham Papers 1921-1980
Graham, Chester A. (Chester Arthur), 1892-
Cooperative leader and liberal activist. Topical files and photographs relating to his work with an Americanization program for immigrants in Akron, Ohio in the 1920s; his involvement in the National Farmers Union, including radio transcripts of programs presented by the North Dakota Farmers Union; and his interest in the Danish folk school movement and the administration of Ashland College in Grant, Michigan; also material concerning the American Friends Service Committee, the Grant Community Church, pacifism, economic cooperatives, and other social and political liberal causes.
85183 Aa 2
15 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection was donated in three accessions, 1979-1980, by Mr. Graham. Donor no. 6420
The collection is open for research.
Chester Arthur Graham was born on March 31, 1892 to parents of Scotch-Irish descent, who lived on a farm near Mercer, Pennsylvania. He received his initial education in the public schools of Mercer, graduating from Mercer High School in 1911. While Graham wanted to go to college, the family's limited financial means required him to work for a time to raise money for tuition.
Initially Graham took to the road as a migrant laborer, following the harvest on the Great Plains. Eventually he found steadier work in Akron, Ohio where between 1912 and 1913, he served as a tire finisher. In the fall of 1913 Graham entered Oberlin College. During his freshman year he developed a deep and lasting interest in religion as a result of a compulsory Bible class. While Graham's father had been a devout reader of the Bible, neither he nor his children attended formal church services. Chester, however, was strongly moved by the words of the Old Testament prophets and began to attend church services weekly. While Graham never developed strong sectarian ties, he eventually became a member of the Society of Friends in 1944, and retained a strong religious element in his thought throughout the rest of his career.
Upon graduation from Oberlin in 1917, Graham volunteered for service in World War I. He, along with other members of his class, served in the Oberlin ambulance unit assigned to the Italian front. Graham served valiantly and was decorated by the Italian government for his heroism, but the experience of war left Graham disillusioned. Returning from Europe he decided that his life should be dedicated to the establishment of harmony among men.
After being released from the military, Graham returned to Akron where he began to work among the city's immigrants. First employed by the YMCA and then, beginning in December 1920, by the public school system, Graham was responsible for Americanization programs. This work led Graham to experience more deeply his commitment towards universal harmony.
Graham's personal growth, however, was not reflected either in the country as a whole or in the Akron area. The nativist sentiment that swept America during the 1920s led to the election of Ku Klux Klan majorities on both the Akron city council and school board. Feeling his work stymied, Graham left Akron and entered the University of Illinois, from which he received an MA in education in 1926 and where he began studies toward a doctorate in international law.
While at Illinois Graham was introduced by an old Oberlin friend to the Danish folk school movement. These schools were dedicated to the broadest possible education for people of all ages and background, unhindered by the conventions of traditional educational systems. In many ways they reflected the philosophy of the free school movement of the 1960s. Graham was fascinated by the school's potential ability to bring together individuals of all kinds. As a result, he spent 1926 and 1927 as assistant director of Pocono's Peoples College in Henryville, Pennsylvania, and in 1928 came to Ashland College in Grant, Michigan.
Ashland had been founded in 1882 by the region's Danish settlers. The school had closed during World War I as a result of anti-foreign sentiment. In 1928, Graham was named both president and resident director of the newly reopened institution. Under Graham the school became a focal point around which persons dissatisfied by America's reaction to the great depression gathered together and attempted to lay the groundwork for a new society. Socialism, unionization of industrial and agricultural workers, and the cooperative movement were all fostered at Ashland.
Graham was least involved in the organization of industrial workers. Many key persons in the unionization of the automotive industry, including Walter and May Reuther, however found their way to Ashland. More importantly, Graham played a role in the creation of cooperatives throughout the state. The Lower Michigan Federation of Consumer Cooperatives was organized at Ashland. Graham's greatest interest, however, was in the unionization of farmers. In February 1933 Graham heard John H. Simpson, president of the Rational Farmers Union (NYU), speak in Lansing. Graham became a devoted supporter of the NFU and in July, 1933 the Michigan chapter of the organization was founded at Ashland. Graham was elected the group's secretary treasurer. Graham remained extremely active in the NFU for the next several years, but eventually he was drawn into an internal power struggle at the national level, resulting in his losing the secretary-treasurer's office in 1936 and his becoming less active in the organization.
While at Ashland Graham was also involved with the local community, most notably by serving as minister of the Grant Community Church, a non-denominational congregation. Throughout his years at Ashland, Graham faced continuing financial difficulties as the school's chief administrator. In 1938 the college faced its final financial crisis when the facility's decaying buildings were condemned. Unable to replace them, the college closed.
Graham left Grant and moved to Madison, Wisconsin, where for two years he served as state superintendent of Workers Education, a WPA funded project. In Madison, Graham also continued with the social activities he had become involved in at Ashland. Most notably, he helped organize a cooperative, and was involved with the Fellowship of Reconciliation, a pacifist organization.
In 1942, Graham reentered the National Farmers Union. He spent 1943 organizing farmers in Arkansas, Mississippi and Louisiana. In 1944 he returned to Michigan where he headed the Food for Victory Committee, a joint venture of the NFU, the American Federation of Labor, the Congress of Industrial Organizations and the Michigan Consumer's League. Graham continued to work on projects sponsored by the NFU until 1947.
In 1948 he moved to Jamestown, North Dakota, at the request of Glenn Talbott, president of the North Dakota Farmers Union, the state affiliate of the NFU. Graham became the radio voice of the NDFU. He broadcast an hour program daily over a statewide radio network between 1948 and 1955. The broadcasts content was left entirely to Graham's discretion.
In 1955 Graham left North Dakota and returned to Madison to become a field representative for the American Labor Education Services. Graham was responsible for convincing local labor unions to integrate material about world affairs into their educational programs.
In 1960 Graham retired from ALES but continued to be active. He quickly found himself executive director of the Madison World Affairs Center. The institution was interested in world affairs, particularly the work of the United Nations, but it also was deeply involved in the civil rights struggle of the 1960s. The Center collected and shipped three tons of food to help feed those in the Selma to Montgomery freedom march. Center members, including Graham himself, personally participated in various demonstrations throughout the South.
In 1966, Graham left Madison and moved to Muskegon, Michigan where he had built a retirement home. While he now increasingly avoided day-to-day administrative responsibilities, Graham remained an activist in liberal causes. He was deeply involved in the opposition to the war in Vietnam. He helped to organize the Muskegon Priorities Council. He also assumed the role of government watchdog, carefully studying a large number of documents discussing governmental activities, including the Congressional Record, and writing summaries of his findings for publication in small journals.
The papers of Chester Graham reflect the multifaceted activities of his career. The papers are arranged in a single alphabetical series, without regard to the chronological relationship between the various folders. Thus material from the late 1970s can be found next to material from the 1920s. In general, folder material begins whenever Graham first became involved with the subject and continues more or less to the present, although material becomes far more ephemeral as time passes and Graham's primary concerns shift to other subjects.
The largest bodies of material deal with Americanization in Akron, Ashland College, the National Farmers Union, and Graham's radio transcripts. There is also a body of material dealing with the Society of Friends and the organization's various political and social activities.
Subjects:
Adult education.; Agriculture--United States.; American Friends Service Committee.; Americanization.; Ashland College (Grant, Mich.); Clergy--Michigan--Grant.; Cooperative societies--Michigan.; Danish Folk School Movement--Michigan.; Denmark--Emigration and immigration.; Farmers--United States.; Graham, Chester A. (Chester Arthur), 1892-; Grant (Mich.)--Learned institutions and societies.; Grant Community Church (Mich.); Immigrants--Ohio.; Liberalism.; National Farmers Union (U.S.); Ohio--Emigration and immigration.; Pacifism.
Subjects - Visual Material:
Adult education.; Ashland College (Grant, Mich.); Calisthenics.; Churches.; Clothing and dress--1921-1930.; Cooperatives.; Danish Americans--Michigan.; Education.; Emigration and immigration--Ohio.; Farmers' groups.; Graham, Chester A. (Chester Arthur), 1892-; National Farmers Union (U.S.); Oberlin College.; Schools--Michigan--Grant.; Theaters--United States.; Theatrical productions.
Genre/Form:
Photographs.
- Alphabetical File
  - A Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Abortion (Box 1)
  - Adult education, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Agriculture hearings (Box 1)
  - Alcohol education (Box 1)
  - Allen, Devere (Box 1)
  - American Country Life Association (Box 1)
  - American Federation of Teachers (Box 1)
  - American Friends Service Committee
    (see also Society of Friends)
    - Chappell, Winifred (Box 1)
    - Dayton, Ohio 1973-1975, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Detroit Friends School (Box 1)
    - Family Camp (Camp Innisfree, Traverse City) (Box 1)
    - Institute (Box 1)
    - Lakey, Berit M (Box 1)
    - Michigan Area Committee 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Mobilization (Box 1)
    - Non-Michigan miscellaneous (Box 1)
    - Peace Committee (Box 1)
    - Quaker Action Group (Box 1)
    - Western Michigan 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Work camp (Box 1)
  - American Guardian (Box 1)
  - American Indians (Box 1)
  - American Labor Education Service
    - Undated (Box 1)
    - 1954 (Box 1)
    - 1955 (Box 1)
    - 1956
      - Exchange of representatives (Box 1)
      - General (Box 1)
    - 1957
      - Exchange of representatives (Box 1)
      - General (Box 1)
    - 1958
      - Cleveland conference (Box 1)
      - Exchange of representatives (Box 1)
    - 1959
      - Cleveland conference (Box 1)
      - General (Box 1)
    - 1966 (Box 1)
  - American Library Association (Box 1)
  - Americanization of Immigrants
    The Americanization of Immigrants material is primarily from the 1920s and includes material relating to the courses taught to immigrants. Mixed with the Americanization material are class papers written at the University of Illinois, apparently based on Graham's experiences in Akron.
    - Adult Immigrant Education
      - Course of study (Box 2)
      - Recruiting and attendance (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
    - Akron, Ohio
      - Annual and other reports, 2 folders (Box 2)
      - Course of study, 2 folders (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
      - Survey (Box 2)
      - YMCA (Box 2)
    - Alien registration (Box 2)
    - Educational Research (by Graham)
      - Educational guidance procedure (Box 2)
      - Immigrant assimilation (Box 2)
      - Immigrant races (Box 2)
      - Nature of educational research (Box 2)
      - Psychology of adolescence (Box 2)
      - Social objectives of secondary education (Box 2)
    - Immigrant legislation (Box 2)
    - Oberlin College (Box 2)
  - Amnesty for President Nixon (Box 2)
  - Anchorage House (Religious community) (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Aage (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Frank (Box 2)
  - Angell, C.F (Box 2)
  - Appleblossom Club (Box 2)
  - Archery (Box 2)
  - Armistice Day Observance (Box 2)
  - Art (Box 2)
  - Ashland College
    The Ashland College material is extensive but fragmentary. While it explains much about the college and its operations between 1928 and 1938, there are also gaps in the records. At best, it is a partial view of the college's work.
    - Articles of Association (Box 2)
    - Courses offered (Box 2)
    - Correspondence undated, 1927-1938, 8 folders (Box 2)
    - Enrollment (Box 2)
    - Financial
      - Undated (Box 2)
      - 1929 (Box 2)
      - 1930 (Box 2)
      - 1933-1938 (Box 2)
      - 1939-1941 (Box 2)
    - Founding (Box 2)
    - Mailing lists, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous written by Graham (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Printed (Box 3)
    - Report to state government (Box 3)
    - Retrospective (1979-1980) (Box 3)
    - Reunion
      - 1958 (Box 3)
      - 1978 (Box 3)
    - Statements of educators (Box 3)
    - Statements of students (Box 3)
    - Summer session
      - 1928 (Box 3)
      - 1929 (Box 3)
      - 1930 (Box 3)
      - 1935 (Box 3)
  - Atomic energy (Box 3)
  - Awards (Box 3)
  - B Miscellaneous, 6 folders (Box 3)
  - Baasch, Hans, 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Barnett, Fred (Box 3)
  - Bergman, Walter (Box 3)
  - Barr, Stringfellow (Box 3)
  - Between the Lines (publication) (Box 3)
  - Bicentennial (Box 3)
  - Biographical and personal (Box 3)
  - Biographies, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Birth control (Box 3)
  - Bowman, Leroy (Box 3)
  - Borbjerg, Viggo (Box 3)
  - Broadcasting (Box 3)
  - Brookwood Labor College (Box 3)
  - C Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Campbell Folk School (Box 4)
  - Carhart, G. (Box 4)
  - Cawthorne, Denis O. (Box 4)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions (Box 4)
  - Character development (Box 4)
  - Child study (Box 4)
  - Christian Century (Box 4)
  - Christian Social Action Movement (Box 4)
  - Churches, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Churches, Muskegon County Council of, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Citizen Participation in Representative Government (Mi.) Congressional District, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Civil Defense (Box 4)
  - Civil Rights (Box 4)
  - Columbia Conserve Company (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth College (Box 4)
  - Community Center Foundation (Box 4)
  - Community Church Workers of the U.S (Box 4)
  - Community life (Box 4)
  - Congressional correspondence (Box 4)
  - Consumers League of Detroit (Box 4)
  - Consumers Union (Box 4)
  - Cooperatives (Box 4)
  - Circle Pines Center (Box 4)
  - Cooperative Family Camp
    - League (Box 4)
    - Lower Michigan Federation of Consumer Cooperatives (Box 4)
    - Local (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
    - Recreation (Box 4)
    - Schools (Box 4)
    - Self-help (Box 4)
    - Wholesales (Box 4)
  - Cousins, Norman (Box 5)
  - Crawford, Walter (Box 5)
  - Credit Unions (Box 5)
  - Crum, C.W (Box 5)
  - D Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Danish Folkehojskole (Box 5)
  - Dannemiller, Larry and Maggie (Box 5)
  - Debt (Box 5)
  - Dechant, Tony (Box 5)
  - Delinquency (Box 5)
  - Delta Cooperative Farm (Box 5)
  - Discussion methods (Box 5)
  - Douglas, Paul H. (Box 5)
  - Draft repeal (Box 5)
  - Draft: Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Box 5)
  - Drama (Box 5)
  - E Miscellaneous (Box 5)
  - Economic issues (Box 5)
  - Educational fraternities (Box 5)
  - Elder, Jo (Box 5)
  - Employment (Box 5)
  - Esperanto (Box 5)
  - F Miscellaneous (Box 5)
  - Farmer-Labor Party of Michigan (Box 5)
  - Federal Council Churches of America (Box 5)
  - Federal Emergency Relief Administration (Box 5)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 5)
  - Flaherty, Helen (Box 5)
  - Folk Festival Council (Box 5)
  - Folk schools
    - Europe (Box 5)
    - United States (Box 5)
  - Folk songs (Box 5)
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation
    - China (Box 5)
    - Conference/Seminars (Box 5)
    - Congressional Interviews (Box 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 5)
    - Draft (Box 5)
    - Drugs (Box 5)
    - Finances (Box 5)
    - International Development (Box 5)
    - Iowa, Illinois and Wisconsin (Box 5)
    - Military (Box 6)
    - Minutes (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 6)
    - Personnel (Box 6)
    - Politics (Box 6)
    - Poverty (Box 6)
  - G Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Geer, Owen (Box 6)
  - George, Henry Pubs (Box 6)
  - Ghosh, Nirva (Box 6)
  - Gillett, Ira (Box 6)
  - Graham, Stella (Box 6)
  - Grand Rapids Peace Movement (Box 6)
  - Grant Community Church
    - Christmas programs (Box 6)
    - Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Easter programs (Box 6)
    - Legal (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 6)
    - Newsletter/announcements (Box 6)
    - Social work Committee (Box 6)
    - Worship service programs (Box 6)
  - Greenfield, Naomi (Box 6)
  - Greyearth, Isaac (Box 6)
  - Gudmand-Hoyer, J. V. (Box 6)
  - Guns (Box 6)
  - H Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 6)
  - Hart, Senators Gary and Philip (Box 6)
  - Highlander Folk School (Box 6)
  - Hilton, Hanna (Box 6)
  - Holcomb, Larry (Box 6)
  - Hole, Francis and Agnes (Box 6)
  - Holt, A. E. (Box 6)
  - Hope College (Box 6)
  - Hutchins, Robert (Box 6)
  - Hutchins, William J. (Box 6)
  - Hutchinson, Carl L. (Box 6)
  - Hutchinson, Carl R. (Box 6)
  - Hyde, A. M. (Box 6)
  - I Miscellaneous (Box 6)
  - Illsley, F. S. (Box 6)
  - Impact (Box 6)
  - Indochina Peace Camp (Box 6)
  - International Year of the Child (Box 6)
  - J Miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - Jensen, Frida (Box 7)
  - Jiriru, Amon (Box 7)
  - Johnson, G. J. (Box 7)
  - K Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - Kagava Fellowship (Box 7)
  - Kane, Mark and Sally (Box 7)
  - Kapnick, Waldo W. (Box 7)
  - Kaufman, A. W. (Box 7)
  - Kennedy, Edward (Box 7)
  - Kerman, Kate (Box 7)
  - Kirkpatrick, Blaine E. (Box 7)
  - Kirkpatrick, E. L. (Box 7)
  - Kirkpatrick, J. E., 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Knutson, Byson and Bernice (Box 7)
  - L Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Labor (Box 7)
  - Land reform (Box 7)
  - League for Independent Political Action (Box 7)
  - League for Industrial Democracy (Box 7)
  - League for Justice to Agriculture (Box 7)
  - Legislative reports (by Graham), 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Leibrand, Dorothy (Box 7)
  - Letters to the Editor, 5 folders (Box 7)
  - Levin, Senator Carl (Box 7)
  - Lin, N. C. (Box 7)
  - Lindeman, E. C. (Box 7)
  - Llano Colony (Box 7)
  - Lloyd, William (Box 7)
  - London Conference (disarmament) (Box 7)
  - Loomis, Ralph (Box 7)
  - Lowes, Elizabeth (Box 7)
  - M Miscellaneous, 5 folders (Box 7)
  - McFarland, Professor E. W. (Box 7)
  - McGovern, George (Box 7)
  - Mack, Nathan L. (Box 7)
  - McLanahan, Jack and Connie (Box 8)
  - McNair, W. N. (Box 8)
  - McNeil-Lehrer report (television program) (Box 8)
  - Madison World Affairs Council (Box 8)
  - Malaiperuman, David (Box 8)
  - Mann, Leland W. (Box 8)
  - Manniche, Forstander Peter (Box 8)
  - Mathiasen, S. A. (Box 8)
  - Menominee Indian Tribe (Box 8)
  - Menon, E. P. (Box 8)
  - Michigan Bureau of Highway Education (Box 8)
  - Michigan Council of Religious Education (Box 8)
  - Michigan Farmer's Fellowship (Box 8)
  - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 8)
  - Michigan Legislature (Box 8)
  - Michigan State Library (Box 8)
  - Michigan Tax Problems (Box 8)
  - Middle East, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Mikvor, Abner (Box 8)
  - Milanowski, Jasiu (Box 8)
  - Military (Box 8)
  - Miller, Herbert A. (Box 8)
  - Missions (Box 8)
  - Mississippi (Box 8)
  - Moller, Aage (Box 8)
  - Money and Banking, 3 folders (Box 8)
  - Mooney, Tom (Box 8)
  - Moore, Dr. Frank Lincoln (Box 8)
  - Morgan, John (Box 8)
  - Mortensen, Enok (Box 8)
  - Morton, Ruth (Box 8)
  - Munk, Arthur (Box 8)
  - Muskegon Priorities Council (Box 8)
  - N Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - National Council of Churches (Box 8)
  - National Council for Prevention of War (Box 8)
  - National Farmers Union
    Material about the National Farmers Union is also extensive but fragmentary. There is a great deal of material about the Michigan chapter of the NFU between 1933 and 1938, including material dealing with the internal power struggle that eventually led to Graham's ouster. Once he was ousted, however, Graham's files become very weak. Even for the period 1943-1947, when he was working directly for the organization, he seems to have either received or retained few documents. In the 1970s, however, Graham began to save most of the printed material sent to him by the NFU.
    - Agriculture (Box 8)
    - Annual Farmers Picnic in Western Michigan (Box 8)
    - Conference for the Protection of Civil Rights (Box 8)
    - Correspondence
      - 1933 (Box 8)
      - 1934 (Box 8)
      - 1935 (Box 8)
      - 1936 (Box 8)
      - 1937 (Box 8)
      - 1938 (Box 8)
      - 1948 (Box 8)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 8)
      - 1969-1971 (Box 8)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 8)
      - 1975-1980 (Box 8)
    - Farmers Holiday Association (Box 8)
    - Farmer-Worker Alliance, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Farmer-Worker Relations, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Farmers and Industrial Workers (Box 9)
    - Farmers and Workers Seminar report (Box 9)
    - Gibson, Harley (Box 9)
    - Graves, Jim (Box 9)
    - Group buying (Box 9)
    - History (Box 9)
    - Junior Farmers Union, 5 folders (Box 9)
    - Kennedy Episode, 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Lee, D. L. publishers (Box 9)
    - Leep, David (Box 9)
    - Legislation (Box 9)
    - Martin, S. P. (Box 9)
    - Michigan, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Michigan Congress of Farmers and Workers (Box 9)
    - Milk (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
    - Nelson, George (Box 9)
    - Nelson, Walter (Box 9)
    - North Dakota (Box 9)
    - Organization, Michigan (Box 9)
    - Pickles (Box 9)
    - Policy statements/Conventions (Box 9)
    - Potter, Keith (Box 9)
    - Publications, 4 folders (Box 10)
    - Puncke, Mary C. (Box 10)
    - Rural Electrification
      - Federal (Box 10)
      - Michigan (Box 10)
    - Union Party (Box 10)
    - Vesecky, John (Box 10)
    - Washington newsletters (Box 10)
    - Wilson, Lucius (Box 10)
    - Yeomans, Mrs. Edward (Box 10)
    - Youth (Box 10)
    - Youth Group of Michigan (Box 10)
    - Youth Week (Box 10)
    - Z (Box 10)
  - National Popular Government League (Box 10)
  - Negotiation Now (Box 10)
  - Negro (Box 10)
  - Nelson, Gaylord (Box 10)
  - Newsletter of the Muskegon Priorities Council (Box 10)
  - Nicholas, Elmer (Box 10)
  - Nolan, A (Box 10)
  - Non-violence, 3 folders (Box 10)
  - North Dakota (Box 10)
  - O Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Oberlin reunions, Class of 1917 (Box 10)
  - Ohio Farmers Week (Box 10)
  - Open House (Box 10)
  - Organic Farming (Box 10)
  - Organic School (Box 10)
  - P Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Page, Kirby (Box 10)
  - Panama Canal (Box 10)
  - Patton, Gerry (Box 10)
  - Paulsen, Ellen (Box 10)
  - Payne, W. E. (Box 10)
  - Peace
    - Academy (Box 11)
    - Advertisements (Box 11)
    - China (Box 11)
    - Committee for Nonviolent Action (Box 11)